<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Phil 160]]></title>
  <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil160/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil160/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-10T23:07:35-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://apc.github.io/phil160/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alejandro Pérez Carballo]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exam Schedule]]></title>
    <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/02/03/exam-schedule/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-03T18:11:53-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/02/03/exam-schedule</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The dates for the first and second exam are now on the <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160/calendar/">course calendar</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readings and First Assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/01/23/readings-and-first-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-23T20:30:44-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/01/23/readings-and-first-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Readings for next week are now listed <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160/readings/">here</a>. The first weekly assignment is also up on <a href="https://moodle.umass.edu/course/view.php?id=13334">Moodle</a>.</p>

<p>Remember that there <strong>will be</strong> discussion section tomorrow. Those of you who have been assigned a different section from the one you originally signed up for should have been notified by email. Please contact your TA if you cannot make it to the section you have been reassigned to.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
    <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/01/22/welcome/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-22T21:14:35-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://apc.github.io/phil160/blog/2014/01/22/welcome</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the website for PHIL 160 at <a href="http://www.umass.edu">UMass Amherst</a>. Announcements, readings, and other relevant information will be posted here. If you are enrolled in this class, you should be checking <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160">this website</a> regularly, as well as the <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160/calendar">course calendar</a>.</p>

<p>For your convenience, I have set up a mailing list for this course. I encourage you to subscribe in order to be notified of announcements on this site. Note, however, that you will only be notified of updates to the site once a day. (If there are no new updates on a given day, you will receive no emails.)</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>I have also set up a <a href="https://moodle.umass.edu/course/view.php?id=13334">Moodle page</a> for this website. However, we will only use that page for two purposes: you will submit your assignments there, and you will be able to review your grades for the course. If I ever need you to check the <a href="https://moodle.umass.edu/course/view.php?id=13334">Moodle page</a> I will make sure to make an announcement <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160">on this page</a>.</p>

<p>(Of course, your TA may well want to use Moodle for announcements to students in his or her discussion sections. Please check with your TA about this.)</p>

<p>If you are enrolled in this class, or are thinking about enrolling, you may want to take a look at the <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil160/syllabus">course syllabus</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
